（タマキ）やってしまったわ。
この私が…。
I messed up... so badly...
Oh? Someone's already here.
（ソウジ）あれ？！　先客がいるなんて。
よし！　決めた。
何を決めたんだい？
Okay, I've decided!
Decided what?
そこ　僕の特等席なんだけど。
That's my reserved seat there, by the way.
じ　軸川副会長！
V-Vice President Jikugawa!
君は　確か…
新しく生徒会に入った…。
You're... new to the council, right?
書記の千枝乃タマキです。
一体　どうしたんだい？
I'm the secretary, Chieno Tamaki.
So what's wrong?
私　生徒会やめます。
えっ？！
I'm quitting the council.
副会長も　お気づきだとは
思いますが　今日の生徒会　議事録。
I'm sure you've already noticed, but in the records of today's meeting,
私は　完璧の「璧」の字を
間違えて　「壁」と
書いてしまいました。
I mistook one character in the word "perfect" and wrote "wall" instead.
そうだったっけ？
はい。
You did?
Yes. As the secretary, I can't allow myself to make such elementary mistakes.
このような初歩的なミス
書記失格です。
困ったなぁ…。
あっ。
This is a problem.
It'd be much more difficult for us if you quit.
君に居なくなられると　困るんだ。
えっ？！
君の字は　とてもきれいだし
言葉の使い方は美しい。
You write very neatly and the way you phrase things is marvelous.
何よりも
文章が読みやすいからね。
It's very easy to read.
居なくなられると困るんだ。
あぁ。
It'll be a problem if you quit.
だから　やめるなんて
言わないで…。
So please, don't quit.
Lost, trying to find it blindly with my hands.
lost te saguri de sagashiteta
tozasareta mirai no kotae nante doko ni mo nai
But the key to the locked future is nowhere to be found.
hashiru shoudou ima kaidoku funou
Undecipherable urges surging.
found kudaketa hazu no unmei wo
I found the fate I believed broken.
mijukuna yume no naka de kikoetekitan da
I heard it in my immature dream.
saigo made I'll be there for you
I'll be there for you till the very end.
tachitomaranai kono hari dake wa
I can't stop. I hear nothing else.
boku no asu wo kizamu oto tsukisasu
How this needle carves my future.
shinjitsu kara nigetara ima
I'm running away from the truth now.
genjitsu ni mo maketara ima
I'm losing to reality now.
nani ga nokoru no (nokoru no)
What will be left?
kazoekirenai kono kizu dake ga
The countless scars on my body
boku no kinou wo zanzou toshite kataru
are the only thing telling the story of my past.
unmei ga hodokete mo ima
Even if fate falls apart now,
sonzai wo kowashite mo ima
even if existence shatters now,
boku no michi wo yuku yo
I'm walkng down my own path.
It's now or never.
This is what they say: "Live your life today."
There will always be, there will always be a way.
Darkness of the Heart
何なの…　これ…　会長は？！
What's going on? Where's the president?
（ピノクル）
千枝乃タマキは　軸川ソウジが好き。
Chieno Tamaki loves Jikugawa Souji.
お困りのようですね…　お嬢様。
You look troubled, young lady.
はぁ　誰？！
Who are you?
（ピノクル）でも　彼は　大門カイトに夢中。
But he's obsessed with Daimon Kaito.
あなたを見てくれない。
かわいそうな千枝乃タマキさん。
He won't even look at you. Poor little Chieno Tamaki.
フフフフフッ　大門カイトなんて…
いなくなれば　いいのにね。
If only Daimon Kaito was no more...
（タマキ）何なの？　あなたは…。
うちの生徒じゃないわね？！
Who are you?
You're not a student here, are you?
学園に…　何の用？
Why are you on campus?
追い出したい？　大門カイトを。
Do you want to chase Daimon Kaito away?
あげる。
えっ？！　な　何なの？！
It's yours.
What is it?
いとしの彼を取り戻すための
お守り…　だよ。
A charm that will help you take your love back.
大門カイト君　私と戦いなさい。
パズルで。
Daimon Kaito!
Fight me with a puzzle!
千枝乃君…　どうして　ここに…。
Why is Chieno here?
（フリーセル）彼女はね　仲間なんだ。
僕たち　オルペウス・オーダーの。
She's now with us, the Orpheus Order.
（カイト）何だと？！
どういう事なんだい？！　千枝乃君！
What?!
What's the meaning of this, Chieno?
（タマキ）行きましょうか　大門君。
パズルは　あの中よ。
Shall we go, Daimon?
The puzzle is in there.
おい！　何　勝手に
話　進めてんだよ？！
Hey, answer our question first!
パズルに挑むのは　大門君１人だけ。
他の誰も　手出しは認めません。
Only Daimon is allowed to challenge the puzzle.
No one else may interfere.
千枝乃君…。
Chieno...
早く行った方がいいと思うよ。
You should hurry.
「裁きのパズル」を拒絶　もしくは
解放できなかったら…→
If you reject or fail to solve the Judgment Puzzle,
あの建物
さっきのパズルみたいになるけど。
that building will turn into rubble as this one did.
（キュービック）そんな…　僕の研究室だ！
（アナ）アナのアトリエが！
My lab was in there!
And my studio!
（ギャモン）あちきの学食が～！
Not the school cafeteria!
私たちの学園が…　でしょうが！
この　オバカサンズ！
You should be worried about the academy!
You three stooges!
ホント　あんたたちは　自分のことしか
考えないんだから！
You really only care about yourselves!
At least worry a little bit about the acad-
少しは　学園のこと…。
待ちやがれ！
Stop!
ウン。
うっ　はぁ。
すぐに　また会えるよ。
裁きのパズルを解けばね。
We'll meet again soon. If you solve the Judgment Puzzle, that is.
何が「裁きのパズル」だ。
Judgment Puzzle my ass.
Why do I even have to fight the vice pre-
大体　なんで　俺が　副会長と！
あっ。
回想
これから　君は　信じていた者に
次々と裏切られ　ゲームを挑まれる。
From now on, you will be betrayed by those you trust,
one after another, as you face the game's challenges.
どういうことなんだ…。
What's going on here?
なら…　確かめるしかねえ…。
I guess I'll have to go see for myself.
オルペウス・オーダーだか　何だか
知らねえが…　受けてやるぜ。
I don't know who these Orpheus guys are, but I accept their challenge.
何のために　こんなこと　すんのか
暴くためにもなぁ！
I gotta find out why they're pulling this stupid shit!
あっ　カイト？！
Kaito!
（ギャモン）
返り討ちに　あうんじゃねえぞ。
Just don't get beaten at your own game!
（フリーセル）ゲームの時間だよ。
It's time to play the game.
（ダウト）先ほどのパズル。
In the puzzle earlier, had his friends come just a bit later,
仲間が間に合わなければ→
あいつは死んでいた。
he would have died.
Is Daimon Kaito really fit for the game as he is now?
大門カイト。　本当に　今のあいつは
ゲームに　ふさわしい存在なのか？
今から　見せてもらうとしようよ。
カイトの本当の実力をさ。
We will see for ourselves
what he's really capable of.
うふっ…　レッツ・プレイ・アップ。
（指を鳴らす音）
Let's play up.
（スピーカー）
（タマキ）「遅いわよ　大門君。　そのまま
エスカレーターで３階通路まで来なさい」。
You're late, Daimon.
Keep going and head to the third floor hallways by escalator.
（タマキ）ルールを説明するわ。
I'll explain the rules now.
This is a maze duel that uses the 3rd to 7th floors of this building.
これは　建物の３階から７階までを
使った　対戦型迷路パズルよ。
君には　これから　ゴールである７階の
エレベーターホールを目指してもらうわ。
Your goal is to reach the elevator on the 7th floor.
建物の中は　区画ごとに　防火扉で
仕切られた迷路になっている。
We turned the building into a maze by blocking certain doorways with firedoors.
迷路のパターンは　Ａ　Ｂ　Ｃの３種類。
There are three maze patterns named A, B, and C.
私は　こちらから
パターンを切り替えるわ。
I'm going to change the pattern now.
（スピーカー）「パターンの切り替えによる
防火扉の開閉時間は　約１０秒」。
It takes approximately ten seconds for the doors to rearrange.
１つの区画で　扉と扉の間に挟まれ
出られなくなったら　君の負け。
If I manage to use the doors to lock you within one area, you lose.
今　君のいる場所から
うまく扉をかわして→
If you can evade the doors and reach to the 7th floor elevator, you win.
７階のエレベーターホールにたどりつく事が
できたら　君の勝ちよ。
対戦型の迷路パズルってのは
そういうことか。
So that's what you meant by maze duel.
A maze that can be changed indefinitely...
切り替えることで
無限に変化する迷路…。
I'll have to remember the patterns and be two to three steps ahead of her,
パターンを覚え　相手の二手　三手先を
読まねえと→
下手すりゃ　永遠に出られねえぜ。
or I'll be stuck in here forever.
副会長！　一つ　約束しろ。
Vice President!
Promise me this:
if I win, you'll explain why you're teaming up with those guys!
（スピーカー）「俺が勝ったら　何で
あんなやつらと　つるんでるのか→
説明してもらうぜ」。
いいわ。
Fine.
パズルタイムの始まりだ！
It's puzzle time!
（スピーカー）「大門君　√学園　校則
第７条　第１項。→
Daimon! Root Academy regulations, article 7, clause 2:
校舎内を走るのは　禁止よ！」。
No running on the hallways.
校則？！
…ったく！　調子　狂うぜ！
Regulations? Gimme a break...
Are you nuts?
なっ　連続して切り替え？！
んなの　ありかよ！
You switched right away? You can do that?
（スピーカー　タマキの声）
「√学園　校則　第１条　第２項。
階段の一段飛ばしも禁止！」。
Root Academy regulations, article 1, clause 2:
No skipping steps on the stairways!
I don't give a damn!
知るか！　あっ。
心の声
ハンパなく　難しいぜ！
このパズル！
This puzzle is insanely difficult!
副会長って　こんなのが
心の声
作れる人だったのかよ！
Since when could the vice president could do stuff like this?
あの連中の仲間ってのは
心の声
マジなのか？！
Is she really with those guys?
いつの間に　パズルを仕込んで
いやがったんだ？
When did they make a puzzle in there?
一体　どうして　こんなことに…。
What on Earth happened to you, Chieno?
千枝乃君…　本当に君は…。
Have you really...?
迷路パターンＡにスイッチ。
Switch to maze pattern A.
ゴールは　この先…。
Ｂパターンでも　Ｃパターンでも→
The goal is right ahead of me.
If this door opens for either the B or C pattern, I'll have no choice but to go.
このシャッターが　上がり始めたら
行くしかねえ。
迷路パターンＢにスイッチ。
Switch to maze pattern B.
（シャッターの上がる音）
よし！
Here it goes!
Ｂパターンだ！　間に合うか？！
It's the B pattern! Can I make it?
間に合わなかったか…。
パターンＣにスイッチ。
I couldn't make it!
Switch to maze pattern C.
（シャッターの降りる音）
やべえ！　挟まれる。
Shit! I'm gonna get caught!
（ピノクル）
あ～あ　逃げられちゃったね。
He got away.
まだまだ　自分の力を
出しきれてないね。
You still aren't using your full power, Ms. Chieno Tamaki.
千枝乃タマキさんは。
えっ？！
もっと　自分を解放してごらん。
自分勝手に　独善的に　わがままに。
You should release yourself.
You should do it your way.
Be self-righteous. Be selfish.
じゃないと　大門カイトには
勝てないよ。
Otherwise, you won't be able to defeat Daimon Kaito.
フン。
分かってるわよ！
本当に　このパズルで勝てば→
I get it! If I win this puzzle, Daimon won't get in the way anymore, right?
大門君は居なくなるんでしょうね。
もちろんさ。
Of course.
あなたたちに協力したのは
そのためなんだから…。
That's the only reason I'm helping you!
居なくなるさ…　もちろん…
この世からね。
He won't get in your way or anyone else's...
ever again.
（フリーセル）数値が　急に上がり始めた。
すごいな。
The numbers have increased.
Incredible. Her brain jumped up to 89% activity in a instant.
脳の活性化率が　一気に８９％だ。
やっぱり　おかしい。
心の声
さっきの副会長…　何か変…。
Something's strange. Something just wasn't right with the vice president earlier.
分かった！
I got it!
何だよ？！　今　忙しいのに！
What do you want? I'm busy!
[TEL]分かったの！
副会長の　いつもと違うところ！
I realized what was strange about the vice president!
はぁ？
[TEL]あのイヤリングよ！
Huh?
It's that earring!
Her... earring?
副会長のイヤリング？
[TEL]√学園　校則　第３条　第１項。
Root Academy regulations, article 3, clause 1:
Rings, piercings, earrings, and other accessories are prohibited.
「ピアス　イヤリング　指輪などの装飾品は
厳禁とする！」。
あのまじめな副会長が
校則を破るわけないよ！
The vice president lives by those regulations! She'd never break a rule!
イヤリング…　あっ。
Her earring...
あれは…　オルペウスの腕輪と同じ…。
Maybe it's...
just like an Armband of Orpheus?
[TEL]そうなの。　私も　そう思うの。
うん。
Yeah, I think so too.
でも　イヤリングの形をした　オルペウスリング
なんて　今まで聞いたことが…。
But I've never heard of an Orpheus ring that looks like an earring.
[TEL]いや　それなら
分かる気がするぜ。
えっ？！
No, I think that's it.
Huh?
オルペウスの腕輪を付けていた俺は
分かるんだ。
I know because I've worn an Armband of Orpheus before.
理性も感情も　何もかもが
変わっちまう　あの状態が…。
It changes your reasoning, your emotions, everything.
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
Academy Puzzle Prize
Winner
Chieno Tamaki
いいパズルだぜ…。
心の声
It's a good puzzle.
厳しいし　細けえし
口うるせえけど→
She's strict, nitpicky, and annoying,
この人の作るパズルたちは
まっすぐで　まじめで　きれいだ。
but her puzzles are straightforward, serious,
and beautiful.
こんなパズルを作る人が　学園を
ぶっ潰すような連中と→
Someone who makes puzzles like that would never join people who are ruining the academy!
つるむわけがねえ！
副会長を　おかしくしているのは
あのイヤリングだ！
That earring is making her act weird!
だとしたら　やばくねえか？
If that's the case, she's in trouble!
オルペウスの腕輪が暴走したら
装着してる人の脳に→
If an Orpheus ring runs havoc, it puts a huge strain on the user's brain!
過大な負担をかける！
副会長が！
危な～い！
The vice president is...
...in danger!
ノノハ君！
あっ。
Nonoha!
[TEL]カイト君　お願いだ！　あの
イヤリングから　彼女を解放してくれ！
Kaito, please save her from that earring!
言われなくても　そのつもりだぜ！
You don't need to tell me!
なかなか捕まらないねぇ！
うっ。
I see you're still having trouble catching him.
このままじゃ　追い出せないよ？
大門カイトを。
You won't be able to get rid of Daimon Kaito like this.
取り戻せなくても　いいのかな？
大好きな軸川ソウジを。
Don't you want to get your beloved Jikugawa Souji back?
イヤ！　そんなの…
絶対に…　イヤ…！
No! I want to... Whatever it takes!
ソウジ先輩…　私を…　私だけを見て。
Souji... Please... Look only at me.
うわっ！　くそっ！
Dammit!
パターンをＢにスイッチ。
Switch to maze pattern B.
96... 97... Forced activation of her brain is over 98%.
（フリーセル）９６…　９７…
脳の強制活性化率　９８％を突破！
Incredible! It's going so high because her opponent is Kaito!
すごい！　カイトが相手だから
この数値が出てるんだ！
（ダウト）フン！
I was right to choose you for the game,
君が　ゲームの相手に選ばれたのは
間違いじゃなかったよ　カイト。
Kaito!
この先が　７階エレベーターホール！
The 7th floor elevator is beyond this door.
ゴールは　この奥…。
The goal is in here!
I'll lock you in this time.
今度こそ　閉じ込めてあげる…。
負けてたまるかよ！
I'm not gonna lose!
人殺しのパズルは　全部
俺が解くって決めたんだ。
I decided to solve all the murderous puzzles myself!
Ｂにスイッチ。
Switch to B.
行くぜ！
Let's go!
（タマキ）大門カイトは　間に合わない。
Daimon Kaito won't make it.
途中で連続して　Ｃに切り替えたら
私の勝ち。
Midway, I'll switch back to pattern C and win.
Ｃにスイッチ。
Switch to C.
（スピーカー）「やっぱり　連続で
迷路を切り替えてきたな！」。
You switched the maze back midway, didn't you?
The door stops for half a second when you switch!
シャッターは　切り替えの瞬間
０．５秒　停止する！　そこが勝負だ！
Victory is mine!
（エレベーターの扉が開く音）
解いたぜ。　パズルを。
I solved your puzzle.
私の手が…　読まれていた。
He predicted my moves.
強制活性化　停止…。
Forced activation stopped.
ここまでか。
It's over, huh?
副会長。
うっ。
Vice President!
そのイヤリングを…。
あっ　私は…　私は…。
That earring...
I... I...
あはっ。
あっ！
副会長！
Vice President!
えっ…　あそこだ！
There they are!
千枝乃君！
Chieno!
しっかりしろ！　千枝乃君！
うっ…。
Wake up, Chieno!
会長…。
President...
私　生徒会をやめたくない…。
I...
don't want to quit the council.
But a vice president shouldn't let their emotions take over like this!
でも　自分の心が
抑えられなくなるなんて→
副会長　失格です。
I don't even know... why I did all that...
分からない…。
私　どうして　あんなことを…。
ふう…　困ったなあ…
君に居なくなられると。
It would be a problem if you quit.
月曜日の議事進行。
水曜日の風紀指導。
The Monday proceedings,
Wednesday's moral guidance,
金曜日の生徒会の議事録…。
and the records of Friday's meeting...
ああ　それから
今日のスクールバスの誘導も…。
Oh, and handling the bus situation this morning.
全部　副会長である君のおかげで
うまくいってるんだから。
It all works out because of you, Vice President.
会長…。
President...
だから　やめるなんて言わないで…
タマキ君。
So please don't quit, Tamaki.
ソウジ先輩！
（泣き声）
Souji!
悪いのは　君じゃない。
君を利用した…　彼らだよ！
It wasn't your fault. It's their fault for using you!
She did a great job.
彼女は　いい仕事をしてくれた。
脳の強制活性化率９８％！
Her brain was forcibly activated up to 98%!
カイトに勝ちたいという思いが
リングに作用したんだ！
Her desire to defeat Kaito activated the ring!
ありがとう。　千枝乃タマキさん。→
Thank you, Ms. Chieno Tamaki.
おかげで　すばらしいデータが
取れたよ！
We got plenty of new data thanks to you!
データだって？！
てめえら　何のつもりだ？！
You were gathering data?
What the hell are you thinking?!
そんなもん　普通の人間に
つけやがって！
How could you put that thing on an average human?!
副会長に　何かあったら
どうするつもりだったのよ？！
What would you do if something had happened to her?
知ったことじゃない。
Like we care.
俺たちが欲しているのは
リングのデータ。　それだけだ。
We're only interested in gathering data on the ring.
We are the Orpheus Order.
我々　オルペウス・オーダーは
偉大なるオルペウスを信奉し→
We follow the great Orpheus,
卑劣なる神々の　くびきから
人類を解放せんとする者。
and aim to free humankind from its cowardly gods.
オルペウスの腕輪を　自らの意志で
捨てた大門カイト。
The one who rejected the Phi Brain, Daimon Kaito...
お前は　進化の可能性を拒否した
人類の敵。
You are an enemy of humankind who rejected progress.
カイト　君には　これから　僕たちの
ゲームにつきあってもらうよ。
Kaito! From now on, you will face our game's challenges.
A game?!
ゲーム…　だと？！　けっ。
それじゃあ　次のゲームで…。
Farewell. See you at the next game.
待て　てめえ！
Wait!
う　ふん。
君は　このくらいじゃあ
思い出さないかな？
I guess you won't remember me from just this much.
僕のことなんて。
何だと？！　あっ！
What?!
Bye-bye.
Who the hell were those guys?
何だったんだ？　あいつらは。
たった１日で　巨大パズルを作り上げ
オルペウスの腕輪で　人を操る集団…。
They made a giant puzzle in one day,
and they use the Armband of Orpheus to control people.
（キュービック）確かに　ＰＯＧとは
違う存在のようだね。
They certainly seem to be independent of the POG.
オルペウス・オーダー。
The Orpheus Order...
eiyuu kidori itsu datte shinjita muteki no kankaku
I think I'm a hero and believe that I'm invincible.
tatakatte iru no wa chikyuu no tame nanka janai
I'm not fighting for the world.
motto mai peesu de
It's for a more personal,
sou motto shoujikina negai no tame
a more honest wish.
nando to naku kizutsuite mo
No matter how many times I'm hurt